好吧，你搞定了
All right, you're done.
我们来看看这个解决方法
Let's look at the solution.
首先我们在AbstractThreadedSyncAdapter中添加一个LOG_TAG
Okay, we'll begin by adding a log tag
in to our AbstractThreadedSyncAdapter.
由于这个玩意是在后台运行的，所以有些log记录是很有帮助的。
Since this stuff runs in the background,
it's helpful to have some logging.
由于我们希望syncAdapter处于无人值守模式
Since we ultimately want the syncAdapter
to run in an unattended mode,
我们从Utility类中提取位置请求，
we pull the location query
from our Utility class, and
然后我们把sunshineService中的代码拷贝进来
then we paste in the code from
our existing sunshine service.
然后我们需要补充一些东西
We'll have to patch a few things up.
我们需要调用getContexts来获得当前的Context对象
We'll have to call get contexts
to get the current context.
比如，我们在getWeatherDataFromJson和addLocation
For example, we copy over
the getWeatherDataFromJson function
中补充getContexts
as well as the addLocation function.
最后我们修改updateWeather来启用syncAdapter
Finally we fix updateWeather
to use our syncAdapter.